I mean, my colleague next to me said that, you know, that we're a foreign-funded organization, right?
Action SA is funded by Martin Marshall, who's Israeli.
And Action SA, Herman Mashaba himself, was found to have put a black box inside of Joburg City Council.
That's a verified fact.
And that box was grabbing information.
It was an Israeli spy machine that was grabbing the information of city councilors.
And there's never been accountability for that.
So when we're talking about elections and who's funding all of this and who's dividing our country and who's dividing the black working class,
it is foreign interests and it is the ruling class.
And it is people who don't want wealth redistribution, who don't want to see the black working class succeeding,
and who are going around, going around, blaming people who, some of them are from Limpopo,
some of them are from rural KZN, excuse me, some of them are from rural KZN, some of them are from the rural areas.
And now all of a sudden, everyone is looking around their neighbors, their neighborhoods and saying,
but that guy has dark skin, but that lady has a funny accent.
This is the perfect strategy to divide the country.
It's the perfect strategy to divide the working class when actually we need unity amongst everyone
to stand up against the system, which is crushing, crushing the black working class and crushing our people.
Sure. So I think Julia keeps reminding us.
Daily Theater, Monday to Thursday from 11 to 12 p.m.
Only on OCBC.
Cut out the corporate middlemen and purchase my music directly from me.
Head to amandadiva.bandcamp.com and pay whatever price you want for Truth Translator.
This ain't a movement, it's movement music.